A Journey Into Iconic '80s Horror
In Search of Darkness is a documentary, horror film directed by David A. Weiner.
An exploration of '80s horror movies through the perspective of the actors, directors,
producers and SFX craftspeople who made them, and their impact on contemporary cinema.
Self, played by Tom Atkins.
Self, played by John Bloom.
Self, played by Doug Bradley.
Self, played by Lori Cardille.
Self, played by John Carpenter.
Self, played by Nick Castle.
In Search of Darkness is a 2019 documentary film
written and directed by David A.
Weiner and executive produced by Robin Block of CreatorVC Studios.
An international co-production of the United Kingdom and the United States, the film explores the development and lasting impact of the horror film genre during
the 1980s, and features interviews with numerous horror icons both from that decade and from the modern era, along with popular horror influencers.
In Search of Darkness premiered at the 2019 Beyond Fest.
The film explores themes of interview, pinhead, 1980s.
The tone is dark.